[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What pet did Samuel Ramos and his wife Lisa buy for their daughter in the 2004 movie Man on Fire?", "correct_answer": "Dog", "incorrect_answers": ["Parrot", "Cat", "Horse"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dr. Quinn, Medicine Woman works in this town.", "correct_answer": "Colorado Springs", "incorrect_answers": ["Boston", "Denver", "Fort Collins"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Three of these Latin names are names of bears. Which is the odd one?", "correct_answer": "Felis silvestris catus", "incorrect_answers": ["Melursus ursinus", "Helarctos malayanus", "Ursus minimus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term Bermuda Triangle was popularized by Charles Berlitz in 1964.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character attacked nurse Ratched, the main antagonist of the novel One Flew Over the Cuckoos Nest, and nearly choked her to death?", "correct_answer": "Randle McMurphy", "incorrect_answers": ["Billy Bibbitt", "Chief Bromden", "Charles Cheswick"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these animals swims the fastest?", "correct_answer": "Dolphin", "incorrect_answers": ["Flounder", "Shark", "Jellyfish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the exact value of the mathematical constant pi, a real number which is in common use in mathematics, physics, and engineering?", "correct_answer": "There is no answer", "incorrect_answers": ["3.14", "square root of ( 16 / (square root of 3) )", "22/7"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these Westerns won 7 Academy Awards?", "correct_answer": "Dances with Wolves", "incorrect_answers": ["How the West Was Won", "Fort Apache", "The Good, The Bad , and the Ugly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The horse of what fictional hero is called Tornado?", "correct_answer": "Zorro", "incorrect_answers": ["Don Quixote", "Don Juan", "dArtagnan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How does prom queen Helen Shivers die in the 1997 blockbuster \u201cI Know What You Did Last Summer\u201d?", "correct_answer": "She is hooked to death", "incorrect_answers": ["She is throat-slashed", "She is poisoned with hydrocyanogen", "She gets hit by a car"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Of the 8 major blood types, which is the most common?", "correct_answer": "O+", "incorrect_answers": ["AB+", "AB-", "A+"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does the myocardium receive stimulation from the nervous system for its contractions?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}]